Whoa, Santa McQueen, oh thank God.
I just needed him to fall into my trap and do that.
Now I never have to talk to him again.
Oh, he's such a bitch.
But you know, it's interesting.
It seems like most of this is stemming
from the AM situation.
I mean, I'm so excited though.
I'm so excited and I just can't hide it.
I'm about to lose control and I just might like it. Oh, we got rid of Alex McQueen
Finally, oh, I hated that guy. I hated him
Now I got the crown on guys we got rid of Alex McQueen forever and
Sing and 300 glow and Sam and and Eldon one. Oh my I'm about to organ
I mean, it's like seriously. We got rid of Alderman one day. They all fell into my trap
Love myself. I'm a genius. I think I might be a genius. They're my crown
Yeah, so guys
Never again. This is an Alexander McQueen free zone free shit Alexander. He's not he's never never
Never again. He's just done. Oh have fun in money for 20s Alexander McQueen
Have fun in money for twins. Oh
My god. Oh, I'm sorry. I forgot that was like the worst dream in the world
Like money for 20 is literally
Booking retarded. It's always that was in between and how much better than some of these people guys
Yeah, it was all planned. It was all it was just a little trap to give them
See the thing is it's like I can't do anything unless they do it first and then I can take action
But if I but if they don't do it then it's like always like a murky area where I can always let him back once he does that
And I don't know why I let him get away with that.
Oops, over before, you know what's happened?
Like last year, when I was like green,
like a little bit green, but he's gone.
I never have to ever, ever, ever talk to him again.
Or say a man, or through your glow, or sig.
I mean, this might just be the best day of my life.
I mean, so I'm gonna crowd myself the king of the trolls.
But I look 65 I look 65 years old. I don't know it isn't a 65 year old
But at least I have one gray hair. I got a little bit more wrinkles than I have
I mean, it's like I know I'm like a little bit, you know, I'm 45. It's like a little bit. I mean, it's like 65
What do you guys think? I like 65 years old
All right
I know I can see another no, oh, let's I love when Sam mentioned the image of me
Oh, by the way, Sam and if you ever show a clip of my channel again, it I'll strike it
I'll strike and same with
Anybody else I don't like
Bye Alex even big Rick big Rick is a troll and big Rick was rootin me
I even hid big Rick for my channel
But then I forgave big Rick because big Rick really didn't do anything that bad
And I'm even about to mod big Rick because I like South Park actually his cartman is my favorite character or butters is
Randy kind of but yeah butters. Oh
Hold on. Bye. Oh, oh bye, bitch
So he's gone guys. I mean, I'm maybe gonna ban. I think I'm gonna name the band. I'm sorry if your name is Alexander or Alessandra
He's a light show. I mean, it's like he's like a non. I mean, he's an asshole
Like the carpenter is an asshole and I like heart man. Not that I'm
Nothing to be weird. Carmen is just a fictional character. He's like he's voiced by an adult
I mean, it's like it means written by adults
I mean it's not fine that now Brandon Hughes gonna go wild. Oh, man. Oh, I need to break here. Oh
My god, he's a pedophile best. He's a pedophile
Q army
Q army. Oh hi. Thank you, Ernie. I got it
I think we did my groove back. You ever see how Stella got her group back. This is how psyche got his groove back
Getting rid of all the
dead weight
I mean some of these people
I mean, they've just been a fucking hair across my asshole.
I'm just waiting for them to fuck up so I can ban them forever.
Actually guys, I'm actually on Colt Codex, I'm creating a page on Colt Codex, I have
the perma-ban list.
I'm gonna be timing you up for that, I'm sorry, I'm timing you up for 10 seconds.
Don't say it again.
Actually, yeah, I'm gonna be bad. I mean, I just like I feel bad for other people named Alex or Alexandra because then it's like
You know, I'm about to ban the fucking name
This just seems like a cursed name for the show. It's not a good name for the show
But yeah, he's gone. So Alice McQueen is gone. Sig is gone. Sam is gone. Elda is gone beat is gone
I mean, I'm just so you if you want to go to theirs. I mean, they're all gonna be over there
I mean, just go over there
I promise you that you won't have as much fun as here.
Hey, it is a good day.
Oh no, oh no, he's back.
If you see him in the chat and there are any guys
just ban him immediately, just ban.
Thank you, mods.
Yeah, not a fling.
So I'm gonna put also on the cool codex,
I'm gonna put the ban list publicly
and I'm gonna put what they did to get banned.
So for example, today, okay, so today's sig.
Or the other day, Sig came on and he had porn as his background.
I didn't, I mean, it's like, I see a little square as like the backstage.
And so I didn't, and then he has like, it's like, it's like,
it was all kinds of different gay porn behind me that he was watching.
I don't know if he was watching or not, but he always was gay porn behind me.
So I let him on and then he's like, oops, I, oops.
And then guess where he was?
He was at the Amazon, at the AM person's chat.
I think for like 10 hours or something human fell asleep and he behaves by in there
I mean he has he's a problem with the n-word here over there. He's just like I think he wants to lick a
You know, I just want to lick. Oh, you know that ams woman's tanked or
And maybe we put inside of her. I don't know maybe what if he's what if he's her baby?
She might put her him
Shit him out and then in Minecraft. I might consider
murdering that
monstrosity
But nothing about any kind of real
Thing we're considering these are just monsters. We're talking about this is not just like it's like I was they called me a werewolf
They're not even a human like talk about not even human. I mean these some of these people
I mean there's a movie. I saw the other day with a really really great friend of mine
And it was kind of about these kind of alien beings
and they were studying humans to figure out
what made the human soul.
And at the end of the movie,
the guy fucking kills the alien
and he's like, you were looking in here,
you should have been looking in here.
Message, there's a message in there somehow.
Cheers, we're doing a celebration.
This is the Alexander McQueen is dead party.
is this is the depth of the Alexander McQueen's.
I mean, just like, fuck off.
Listen, Alex, Money420 has a panel.
You're making him deals to fuck up my panel now,
which you can't even do
because I'm too quick for you to just slow and dumb.
Like, I guess a lot of people with Alex in their name
or something.
I think they're just like mongoloids at this point.
But that's what basically my intention was for was today because I had an interesting day starting started early
started with
I'm not even gonna say what I did, but I'll give you a little hint and end it with the same thing, but
Basically, I was told or basically I wasn't even have to be told I was just I just understood finally
You don't need some of these fucking losers
You're above them
insignificant and the real ones
See the real ones I can get into an argument have disagreements with and it's like and then I'll get upset too
And that just means I really love them these people. I was waiting for them
To fall to the trap and they're so dumb they fell into it
Okay, I'm gonna mod big Rick
Big Rick. I like you. I do like video unavailable. Did I get a strike?
My goodness, obviously I didn't because I would have my not be able to stream on this channel
But let me just check and I did not receive a strike. We see oh
Interesting interesting. I just got some very good news
very good news
There's even more of a celebration. I guess I'm some very good news. I'll just I'll say that for the people that are my friends
You'll be happy for me
For the trolls you'll be furious. And so it's a win-win for psyche, right?
It's just a win-win
It's like a double double you which would be like a
Kind of like oh, yeah, the Alex took another L and it goes
Okay, first of all ghosts. I do want to say and I'm your modded ghosts, okay?
I'll keep you modded, but I have a few rules for ghosts ghosts
You're always on my TOS and stuff
Ghost your band from using the n-word the f-a-g-g-o-t
from complaining about
my music
otherwise
Have fun. I mean that I mean it's like I mean it's like I really don't have all my only rules are against us
And just basic human respect
If you can keep that
You can keep your mod
You can't
You're gonna end up on the shit list, which is gonna be on cold codex and it's gonna detail every fucking of their violation
For example, so I told you about sick what he did, you know, he put on porn on the back and then he blamed me
For saying well, you brought me up. Well, I didn't see you had porn behind you
I mean, I saw a bunch of like, you know gay guys faces, but I didn't see they had dicks in their mouths
I didn't know you were watching Gay Porn and stuff.
I love you, I love you.
I, okay.
I didn't know that sick.
You know what 300 Glow did?
And 300 Glow, who I liked.
And he said he wanted me to fuck them and stuff
and have a threesome with his wife.
And I think that was all maybe just lies.
Because you know what he did today?
He put a, he put a fucking, I mean, I left the stream.
I said, here, I trust you'd have to be on,
be alone in the stream.
He put a gun to his head.
That's gonna be this is a former band pretty much
anything
Complaining about any of my of my content
Perm a band anything porn bombing perm a band. I
Just have to be strong. So I'm also I have some news for you two guys
I decided to kind of step a little bit back from streaming
Not fully but I was thinking
In the future, I was thinking Monday, Wednesday, Friday,
one to two hours, however I'm feeling,
and maybe more if I'm feeling more,
but it's up to my discretion.
I mean, it's like whenever I feel like it,
whenever I fucking feel like it.
And then on the weekends, I'm thinking like,
this is just a little rough outline
enough to give too much away.
On the weekend, maybe like a two, three hour stream.
One of the days.
Oh, Sam-Anne's ban too,
because Sam-Anne and Eldo are scamming on Cash App.
And if they've scammed you, I will give you,
and this will be a no charge,
I will give you some free advice on how to retaliate.
Legally, all within the thing, if they did you wrong,
I'll tell you how to, I can have,
yeah, I'm gonna have Sundays off.
Okay, every day I have Sundays off.
Okay, well, I'm thinking, I'm just saying,
maybe I'll do an hour a day with six days a week,
but it's up to me, it's up to me, really, ghosts.
That's what I mean, well, you want me back?
I thought ghosts was over me.
You still like me ghosts? I know I told ghosts leave me alone and stuff. You know, I didn't mean it really but
That I like ghosts. He's mad that I made this little cartoon of him and he's like I'm doxy him
But he looked goes excuse me. You're a really cute cartoon
Be proud of yourself and plus for the fan. Okay. Okay for the fan. Well, I mean if the fans want more
They can give me a little bit more because it's like a lot of energy. I put in a lot of time energy thought
love I put in
For not very much return like it pretty lately except from a few really really
really good friends, okay, and so
I'm gonna keep my schedule, and if you want any more than that
there's a cash app
You can request me to go on and stuff like that, but don't ask me to do things without
Remembering that it's an energy exchange. It's not just like, oh, I'm your puppet because beat it tonight
Cuz so I was on Zayas of the other night and I like Zaya
And I don't believe he's a PDF or anything like that. I like him still. I mean, he was really really really
Rude to me after I've been really and I but I forgive him because I wasn't perfect with him either. I
Love listen, I love Peppies
Okay, I like I'll say I'll you know as a friend as a she just thinks I just never had a negative
Interaction with her and she's you know and she's with her boyfriend and you know
He's her boyfriend and stuff and stuff, but I like her a lot
Not I'm almost a maybe not say love, but I love I do very much like her
It's a fellow streamer, and I like Sam
And I don't think he had a gun and I I don't think he's a PDF because he let a 19-year-old move in with them or
Whatever, I don't I just like you know what fuck that
Everyone makes a big deal out of fucking a mountain out of the molehill
Okay, it's this is bullshit most of it, right?
I mean, it's like yeah
So they can go to those channels.
I'm not gonna be on those channels anymore.
I'm not gonna be on beatas anymore.
I'm not gonna be on salmon.
I'm not gonna go places where they're like,
I wanna at least, I don't need a red carpet thrown out,
but I wanna at least like a magenta one or like,
not even a carpet, yeah, mind your business, right?
I have to mind my business.
Hey, listen, I have to eat too, right?
I could call, I could call all kinds of things and stuff like that.
I mean, there, there are literally people like, they could think of it like Logan Paul who just has his, the world is a oyster.
He's a billionaire. He's literally a billionaire.
And people are sending him like probably a couple hundred thousand donations and stuff like that.
I'm like, you know, basically starving to death, almost.
And it's like, then, oh, I'm e-begging.
I mean, so it gets kind of weird.
And I mean, this is so projectionist.
Guys, understand there's so much projection.
Jealousy misplays hatred, projection.
Listen, are these people on camera?
Look at the, first of all, just question.
Are they on camera?
I mean, any of this.
I like you mad hat. I like you mad hat and things around saying bring back Alex or whatever with the link
Okay, okay, go see
You don't know I like you mad. I'm not in a gay way. I do you like I do like evolved guy
The thing that is is pretty much fulfilling my fantasies that and which are not very
Diamond fancies they see an almost a nightmare
Okay, but and I will I'll leave your butt alone. Okay, if you really if you don't if you don't mention
I know, and if you don't mention Alex and Sam and these assholes I won't look at your
butt.
I won't even look at it.
It won't even be a thought in my mind.
I can't promise it in my dreams, but okay, I'm just kidding.
Are you a real doctor, Manhattan?
I need a prostate exam.
I'm so sorry.
Hey, I'm having a celebration night.
Get up here, ghosty.
Get up here.
Where are you? Did I put the link up yet? I love you, Ghosty.
I love Popsicle Toes. I love, um, I strongly like Daryl.
Matt Hatton, he doesn't, last time I, I tried to give Matt Hatton like a mod, just like,
because this is a show, a show of grace.
And then he, he hid my nightbot.
I mean, that was an app, that was a dick move.
But you know what I figured out? How to get past that, Matt Hatton.
I made him a managing moderator,
and so you won't be able to ever do that again.
Only certain special people will be able to hide my thought,
and they wouldn't do that.
You have a guest come on the show.
Let's welcome, hold on, I need to pull up a song.
I need to pull up a song.
This is my introduction song for this person, okay?
Bear with me.
Don't get afraid, don't be afraid.
I mean, I know you don't want it. Okay. You're about to get hit in. I just told you I'm not giving you one
I said I tried to give you one and then you hid my nightbot. You won't be getting one again
I need to play the introduction song. So this way backstage person
Dr. Matt Haddon, don't fuck with me, please
Listen, it's not the time. This is not the day or the time
My name is nothing year. Let the sun
You don't want me there. I'll see here's a way Darrell. You don't want one?
I have permission to crush on you.
I don't know where you are, you don't hear what I'm saying.
Heroes are loud like thunder on caffeine
Dropping stacks, cracking jokes
Keeping the scene clean
The crowd starts howling
The trolls start crying
Ghosts just grins
Let's fucking go chaos
But the hail from the sky lost its hue
They can't see the light he threw in my storm
But I remember I was reborn
May I have permission to crash out?
every hater when the chat brings it loud it's closed over baby psych he's proud
they talk slick why is he still around for kindness is rare on this battleground he saw my fault
still chose to believe most just lie and chose to leave me is the king rational is so horny
in a world full of clowns he's the last to fake when the screen went
dog kept me awake all the nades but ghost remains turning pain into a digital flame may i
permission to crash out you already know ghost runs this town you already know ghost runs this town
you already know ghost runs this town fucking go becomes a dream dumb dumb to the ones who doubt
Yo, I gotta get some credit work to do. That is a damn good song. Thank you. So I'm not all bad, right?
Not all bad. I mean, after that song, I mean, you try to soften me up when I came, that's why you
played that song. Hey, I'm just, hey, I'm gonna. Damn good song. I have an idea. I'm gonna do these
intro songs and give, give my guests a good introduction from now on. I love you too. Maybe,
Maybe a son of the full song. Maybe like, you know, like
Well, I deserve it obviously yeah
Train it's early in the morning busy around here. I hear that train every five minutes when you're on the phone though
Yeah
By the way, psyche night
People accuse me of that. Oh, you're pushing a button. No, I don't do that. I thought I was talking. It's actually a fucking real train station. I
Love you. Don't try to Google it. No, I'm tapping into Alec. Hey, what up? What up, Kat? Good Darryl
You know that cat kind of reminds me of
The I don't know what breed is but they show it in like movies and Celtic Beach. Oh, I like the old
Older species like the Egyptians. I don't know the Egyptian cats
Okay, yeah, but I mean that kind of is a sore subject because I've already been said that
Sacrifice my cats because the Asian Egyptians did well. They say they say I f4 dogs. I mean
They say a lot of shit is a
Your mom came in the room and you said I'm I'm effing the dog, but it was a joke. I understand here
I mean if they mad by the way, they're saying people that will go on a panel and talk all this shit and say like oh
Like if they'll literally they will literally say that I'm bad
That's what they do. They let me on the panel and guess what they don't be fun
They can't be from their position and I destroy them every time right?
You got me something very important. It's like I've been telling you this for like
Right the burden of truth
Yeah, you need to learn how to debate a little bit
I'll say one thing goes
Probably the worst debater I've ever met but you do know that one that one thing
Okay, let us assume, you know what for argument's sake. I'm not up here to argue
I'm just here to argue. Let us just okay for arguments. Let us let us assume that I am the worst debater that you ever met
Let me make a response to that
Check the score. I've won how many I've won more than I've lost. I can't be that fucking bad
Dumb dumb
Let's fucking go
I'm just gonna let you have your moment right now goes just go ahead and have your moment
I mean, I could I could bring up some shit, right? I could like old name one debate. I've ever lost
You're not gonna be able to do it. No one ever is
I'm not I'm not going to be able to do it
This is a lot of people like, you know, I'm not talking about you
But a lot of people like you're the worst debate or you've never wanted to be
I'm not talking about you. I'm not talking about you. I'm talking about
You're not the worst. You're not the best by far
I'm but I mean amateur. Can you give me amateur? Yes, you're an amateur debate
You know what I think by the time this live ends you might be Sam the best debater
No, it's the funny thing those like I join other lives and shit like they always talk
Stuff and then like I'm like all you gotta do is put their feet in the fire is like
You know what they would never do they never they'd ever know they're like
It's hard to prove these things to them, but it's okay. It goes. It's okay
Well, I think when especially I'm like bigger like if you're on like a big platform because I was even on
Dusty's platform, uh, the public donor who
Yeah, I brought his ass up and I actually took it
Yeah, he's after Charlie, but I want to say one thing. Well half
Everyone in this chat that I haven't
Hidden and including ghosts you're all in my heart. It is like and I'll always
Everyone here that I haven't hit him really
Isn't that so funny that Alex was hiding me and then like
Well, no one likes that well, here's the reason why I like beating up on Alex
I even like occasionally talking about believe it or not
Here's his number one problem. He p-bombs and he's been known to do it. No, no for the problem is he is
I mean, I mean, it's a problem you said we can't say that word. You said we have a signal
You can say recharge on this show. It's not I mean, it's your life. You can do whatever the fuck you want
You know, you're not sure you're charged. Just say f-a-g-g-o-t and don't say the n-i-g-g-e-r
Okay, this those two rules. Okay, don't say those two words. I think those are the only
Yeah, I mean and it but I'll say I'm gonna make it very known
People that say those words
And I don't even like the NIGGA that maybe is a gray area, but I'm going to say if you say
It depends we grew up at like
Is fine, okay, it's gonna be okay, but if you say NIGGR or if a GGOT on the show
Yeah, my biggest thing is like I'm a free speech uh advocate like I believe in free speech
I'm not doing your pain. I'm the same in general
I'm a free speech advocate as well, but you can't do it on YouTube obviously, you know
YouTube is his own his own
Yeah
The only thing that's worse than YouTube is tick tock that they'll get you for saying like like a s.i.m.p
Just recently that didn't get taken off immediately
I'm a streamer named Perez Hilton
Cut him. Oh, yeah, he didn't he freak the fuck out. Yeah, he started cutting himself with a knife and stuff
I don't know if it was real or not, but he started cutting himself on the stream like okay
I've been on tiktok live and
Listen, I was gonna take that live with the cigar right here and like the cigar
Instantly like seriously, I've lit a cigarette on on you shoot on tiktok live
Instantly it's age-restricted to take it out of the algorithm
He didn't have her mission sham. He didn't have her mission. You know what?
Goes did Perez have permission to crash out? No, you know who gives no, he didn't he should have asked for mission
I know you know the one person information is ghosts with my yeah
I would I would have given permission to crash the fuck out. Actually. I don't know because I didn't watch it
Have you seen the movie called no country for old men
Oh, yeah, that's a great fucking movie
It's a Tommy
And then it's Thanos to just brawling or whatever he was in the doonies
Melee Jones there it is. I just thought of that
Tommy Jones in a drop bro. It's great movie by the way, dude
That dude is a legit like they say there's no such thing as a psychopath anymore. They can't diagnose it
That dude was a psychopath
the bad guy. I forgot what his name was, but the bad guy, that was a legit psychopath.
I read the book. There's a book too. Did you know that? You read the book too.
Let's see. I have a special friend now, and I'm not going to get too far into it,
but I have a special friend. We have movie nights.
I love movie nights, man. What's that?
Might as well. I love moving nights. Good. I think I'm gonna do a booby nights on my my
Discords or something like that once in a while. Yeah, I think a good idea for me and you like when October comes
We watch like Halloween movies like ghost over
Okay, do you like do you like the Halloween series or do you like Freddy? Oh, yeah, of course
When I was a new one was the newest one was pretty pretty damn dumb
Why do you like how I mean what I like? I like that when okay name your number name your number one best
Halloween movie because I got mine. I know
It plays on 59th Halloween, or 39th Halloween.
Okay, there's a movie about Halloween night,
which is a really good movie,
but that's like very kind of obscure.
I'll say Nightmare on the Shoot.
But guess what?
You should know that I always call your cat.
A certain name.
Salem?
Hold on.
Yeah, Salem.
But I call your cat a factory beaks.
Oh, oh, oh, it's that, it's that,
focus, focus.
Yes, sir.
So that's also really engineering. I saw hocus pocus when I when I was like, you know, I came out when I was born
I think I think it came up in my mind. Well, I know
I was probably 12 years old and I'm probably four years old older than you I was the price while we're low when I saw that
Do you know what that had a woman? There's this fat slob
In Boston Bridget, but she goes to like Sam ends the stuff and she was actually threatening me with her say
Not be to her name is Boston Bridget, but she but she was ready. She's a I'm gonna say my my Salem ancestors up you
And you know, I have Salem ancestors
Well, you believe in that which I don't I don't believe you believe that witchcraft shit. You can probably battle her
I don't I believe in Jesus Christ, sir. Hey, I believe in Jesus Christ, too
Hey, listen to me listen to me. She goes don't the one thing I'm never gonna do is say you're this or that or what you believe
Okay, yeah, but you believe in me because I love I
Love like be Jesus my homeboy in a certain way. I thought you ever say I didn't say you didn't believe in them
I just don't want to talk to you like that goes you ever see
You can't I think champ ever seen Jesus Christ super star ghost
I don't believe so that was like 1973 and then it was I think it made into a Broadway play or something like that
I saw that recently. It's a musical and
And it's a beginning of being a musical this bus goes in this desert and has this cross
Let's jump to the top of the bus with all the props and everything and
John James, how are you? I'm gonna mod Shawn James to because Shawn does the front if you don't mind Shawn
You don't I did not here. Who do you mind?
I'm Shawn James
John John Mike John
Yeah, Mike Jones. That's exactly what bro. You talk about like a musical with Halloween stuff. Have you seen like that?
It's I don't know what it's called. It's not pretty excited. It's a girl from
She's very popular, you remember the sweet life of Zack and Cody or whatever, like the
one twin still acts, the other one doesn't, help, okay, I'm going to make you a mod.
Okay, so that was a little bit, to Zack and Cody, I think those were the twins from Full
House, if I'm not mistaken.
Yeah, the one brother still acts, the other one don't act anymore, I guess.
Right?
Right back, Dreyer modded too, he was the dude in Five Feet Apart, but he has that movie
It's called something, and it's like a musical, it's weird.
They did that with Joker too.
I think the youngest show I watched was the adventures of Pete and Pete.
How old are you?
I'm 45 years old.
Goddamn!
I'm old. I'm an old guy.
Like, but, Ghost, how old do I look?
Because, you know, because RG and other people are saying
I look 65 years old or older.
You're about 55.
Hey, look, I'm doing 50s.
Okay, well, I'll leave it at that.
If you look, RG, you look 30s, low 30s, 32s, 33s.
How old am I, 30s?
Maybe, yeah.
Ghost, I'm about to give you a hug.
Okay
Hey guys guys, I mean 25 that's very very I wish but you know, I was told like 65
So so so they're aging me 40 years just to hurt my feelings, right?
Well guys, I haven't seen like a 65 year old like man like you know what they're
Well, you know, I think I think I look good for my age. Maybe I'm a little bit
You're like you're like late 20s early 30. I look in my 20s
What the fuck? What the fuck? Okay, okay, so it's late 20 early. That's not thinking man. Why are you being weird about it?
Hey, hey, dry a thing that is
This is celebration night and you get her you get I know you don't want it you don't have to use it
This is just a sign of respect for you to say. I mean at least you got an age
I asked how I looked on the panel last night. They said fat
Hey goes is it rain coming by again?
Goes do you ever get on that train?
Goes have you ever ridden that train?
The long black train you don't go riding that brother. Okay. Okay. Oh, I don't want to get a little
I'm not getting to that but I wanna know that was religious that wasn't I yeah, yo that was religious
Josh Turner song. So it's the thing that is there's been a few people banned from the pick banned from my show
That is you know what? I'm a moderator block. He's getting blocked. He's a moderator, too
What was Alex seems a step above the moderator will do Alice wasn't I always let him think that he was he was never a
Bandaging moderator. He was always a standard moderator, but now he's been yeah, I'm a moderating. I'm a moderating moderator
I'm moderating the moderators.
You're in block thing, that is.
I want to invite 10 people that are banned permanently
from the show today.
Samman, Eldo, Sig, Rihanna Glow, Alex McQueen.
Those are like the five that's strong in my mind.
What did Samman do?
Samman scammed your nation.
Yeah, man. Yeah, and he scammed me for a donation. Him and Eldo
said, oh, we'll give you a catch up for this and then Eldo said, oops, I accidentally said this.
By the way, I think SIG and 300 go are the same person. I don't know. No, they're not the same person.
I mean, I've seen them separately, but
yeah, to be banned, you actually have to be bad and it's like, so you know what 300 glow did on my show today?
Well, I mean Alex P bomb and even
I'm just asking you know 300 gloated him on show today. No, but please tell me you put a revolver to his head when I went off
the panel for a second. Oh, that's real smart. It's real smart
God and it's like and this is like guys. I really I've been through enough at this
You can't even show that on YouTube you give him a show a
Yeah, just tell me about it. Tell me about it. I got enough in this YouTube game
to fuck him
Finally have a zero-tall because I'm so forgiving. I looked them back on. Yeah. Listen. Listen
I'm gonna have a page on code codex
With the permanent ban list and these people are just if you see them anywhere near the stream
Don't even say don't don't mention don't reference them. Just hide them mods. Okay?
You've got to remember when you get like a mass on band you can't on band in you got to remember that
I will. I mean, it's like, but I've been having it on Cold Codex,
and so I'm just gonna have my Cold Codex do it.
Thing is, it's on a dating show.
So I believe there's certain things like I believe an evil obviously I'm a Christian
I believe evil and I believe there's some people are evil. I believe they're people that do show up
I think there's people that
It goes people that are evil demons. I do believe in demonic possession and whether it's just like
I'm psychological or it's like they're on some kind.
It's a cool thing.
I do too, but how would you ever fight against that?
Ghost, do you want to see it?
How do I fight against it?
I have moderation tools.
But Ghost, do you want to see yourself on Coke quick
when it says about you?
I don't think I've ever read you before.
Ah, you might as well.
Okay, this is the Oracle,
and I'm going to read you next time, okay?
So this is called Codex right here.
And everybody-
What was that?
You just said?
The Codex.
I'm gonna read here.
I'm gonna have that Oracle read you.
Oh, the Codex.
The Codex.
Okay, so there's the Oracle.
We're in.
So you see it?
Okay.
So I'm gonna say ghost, okay?
Ready?
Codex is thinking.
Okay, so ghost lives as the rupture invader,
a whispered presence, psyche summoner.
Mm-hmm.
then labels as cool after resolve rupture and later notes the discrepancy or MIA status.
The archive records ghosts as both a little participant, one spoken to alongside Joe in
later absence, and as a metaphorical draft of the cell, the unpublished ghost in one's head
that is not an enemy. The duality folds ghosts into the inner circle, crossing the threshold
from a peripheral echo to named entity that shapes the show's mythic and interpretive layers.
each invocation marks a shift in psyche's narrative,
turning a spectral rapture into a relational anchor
for the community. The ghost is the rupture that becomes the rule.
Okay, so there's the ghost. I'm going to read to Jan now. You like that?
I did. Can I respond? Sure.
Oh, yeah, the last time I looked it up. They uh, it said I was a lion and I and also
There are no and I read a quote
They also said Achilles and there's a quote that actually said there's no past between lines and men
There's no past between line and prayer
I just remember remember you didn't text message me once and said you wanted a reading on the show
And I was like, well, I'm not doing a show tonight, but I'll give you a reading and you came up
No, if you didn't have a show why don't you forget on the show about what I come?
No, no, do you remember what card came up for you that I sent you a picture of?
Michelin tireman no
Achilles that would be that would be realistic
But it came up was King John from Robin Hood who is alive was rude if I put up a card for you
No card you'd get what the Joker and not in a good way
It's a dating show. Hey, we have a guest here. Okay, so that is that out. It looks like Alex McQueen though
It's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it
And, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and, and
Alex is the type of person like, um,
I love him a hole.
Listen, listen.
He put him in a hole.
He couldn't, and he pulled himself.
And he did it for money for 20.
You can't throw him a shovel because he'll start digging his own grave.
He'll literally dig his own grave.
Yeah, but listen.
And then he did it for money for 20.
Money for 20 is like literally the lamest ass.
Ooh.
Ooh, yeah.
Okay, Alex, this is backstage. You can just circle off from backstage, but I guess can't do it right now
Especially not in the show going celebrate. Please don't put it on this
I know I know he now is it now. He's upset now. Yeah now. He's upset. It's okay. What are you doing?
What is that? Okay, Alex, I
Don't mind talking to you on a personal level, but I like I do like you. I think you're a little bit too
Restart it much for the show. I don't I don't know is it is a I think I would like I like you as a person
And I'd be happy to talk to you as a person. I think you're upset because you got unmodded and you said you were not a ghost
Letting him back in the chat and stuff like that, but it's like I've been through so much with him for a bit of big black dick
On my screen and then start laughing about it. I don't hurt my feelings. Hey, but we have a dude
We have a very sexy guest coming on right now. Mmm. Oh
He's beautiful. I have a song for him. Actually, I don't know why he's like the background
He wants the introduction song. He decided he was like saying yes, he wants the introduction song
Okay, let's play the introduction song. I won't play the whole thing. I'll just play a little bit. Yeah, you might as well
Yeah, play the best part, you know
If you can't okay, I'm a whole I'm right this month. This will take like 10 seconds. I have to go to my
Okay, so this is I'll actually this whole thing home. Okay. This is
I was thinking about you earlier today. It's like yeah, I got a new coloring thing on my phone and
Like I just colored pictures on my phone, you know quick test like paint my number basically on your phone
Here you go
I'm gonna bring them up very disrespectful place on at the same time get up here get up here bro
Now I'm finna have to run one with you
Hello
Hello guess what this is good morning. Oh my god. It's America. Oh my you get out of here
He'll twist your view, but he'll smile when he knows he's got to make me do.
Think that it's steadiest.
Art is the stars, but never alone.
That carries his name
There's an old thing right there
There's a little bit
Oh, this is a sexy song
It's like that name
It doesn't matter
To the world's loud room
He stands his ground
Clears the gloom
See that ghost, I got a sexy song
A sexy song, guys
I got an Indian song
Yeah
And still wish you
I still won
At the end of the fight
Steady as stone, I get the stars that never go, generous heart, never cruel or mean, searching for truth, somewhere between me and my life, I like a lot of songs, I like a lot of songs, I like a lot of songs, I like a lot of songs, I like a lot of songs, I like a lot of songs, I like a lot of songs, I like a lot of songs, I like a lot of songs, I like a lot of songs, I like a lot of songs, I like a lot of songs, I like a lot of songs, I like a lot of songs, I like a lot of songs, I like a lot of songs, I like a lot of songs, I like a lot of songs, I like a lot of songs, I like a lot of songs, I like a lot of songs, I like a lot of songs, I like a lot of songs, I like a lot of songs, I like a lot of songs, I like a lot of songs, I like a lot of songs, I like
he still gives maybe some woman who sees what i see the brave kind of gentle that lets other
warm in the cold worth more than gold he fights for death stands for the true and ends its way
to you so raise a glass to the north
To the man who argues but gets it right
That he is! That he is!
No, this one is trash.
Mason, I'll make you a deal, Mason.
You know the thing that is, I got a problem with that.
My song gets people going. That song gets people going to bed.
Mason, the only problem is that it gets people going what?
My song gets people going. Your song makes people want to go to bed.
No, man. My song is sexy and sultry. Give me a break. Yeah
Right because you can't hide in that is anymore by the boot by sleep
Some so the thing is Mason won't give you any more problems anymore. Remember when he was hiding you
Alex, yeah, no, no Mason was no Mason Mason was y'all that was so long ago and it was only okay once
Two questions for a thing that is
Hey Mason, how are you?
Listen, here's my my goal is to make everyone a moderator to be able to trust everyone here as a moderate. It's my goal
Yeah, good luck with that
Listen thing that is are you storm vacation?
No, he got back from Mexico about a month ago goes to me. Come on. Oh my bad. I'm a year late
How's your dog by the way, is your dog okay mine? Yeah
Okay, Arthur, I'll make you a deal Arthur
No talking about my content like my music and stuff. No, I'm promoting Sam-Man and
Be an office rules. Okay, I'm not banning hammer and no being Canadian
But oh, I might ban hammer, but hammer had a sex change so they might be a little bit
I know no being bold but the deflated boo that they had either the public
Actually, I have a band. I have a hammer band and so see that's the funny thing is that I can just like hide people
And so they'll never be an even consideration for a moderator
They can just talk in the chat and let it talk to the boy. Other people can see their comments
I just won't and other mods can hide them if they are
Music listen, I figure out the system listen. I'm beating the system
Hey psych I had a personal thing. What are you wearing your necklace like that? I'm sorry
I meant to wear like this
No, I'm sorry, that's not right. Oh, I'm gonna put that as a crown but
I'm like, yeah, it's like without saying names dude. I had people are females by the way
They were calling me there's multiple by the way multiple females call me about you. I mean, I know you
Like why do you let that bitch join I was like
My me about you
We're you walking on my handsome motherfucker. That's why it's we're calling. I annexed is a very
Controversial you shouldn't mention
That's a hurt
Next and for the morning
Sending her to a panel and then abandon her there. It's a random panel
That's not sure if you're gonna you're gonna have to bring context of that. No, I don't
I know you like you do to me. I invite you to panels. I think you're I know I know and then you leave me there alone
And I'm like, why am I here? Where's ghost you're off somewhere else?
Well two hours later. Yeah, we have to leave at some point
It goes, it goes, do you ever snort coke on your toilet and forget things?
I do not I started a lot of coke whenever on my toilet. I mean, I started on my toilet
You've never done coke off the back of the toilet
Like you've never been out and done it is what I'm getting at
My card works just fine
I don't want you to fucking use a toilet.
Yeah, but, Gose, do you need a Coke?
I'm getting angry.
Gose, can you get a Coke and can I come visit you
in wherever you are?
You know what you probably should come to me now. You know, he's been like a
First of all, I want to see what
You'd be the greatest amateur debater I've ever heard
First of all, I want to go to Canada and I want to meet Paige and think that is
and go to the Rockies. Is it the Rocky Mountain?
Yeah, Page is much closer to the Rockies than I am.
Okay, but can I visit you? Do you think I'd just stay with you and your mom?
Yeah, I think that it's good.
But we're not close to Page.
I know, but...
Okay, okay. It's a cross-country trip. That's all I'm saying.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I'm going to go to you and then Page.
Okay, then I'm gonna go to the um, this I don't know why you're trying to be funny right now
I told you if you ever we ever came to visit each other. We could work three men
I want to go to the arches of st. I'm in st. Louis
Had to say Missouri Missouri. Yeah
And go to this I want to have I want to have a romantic dinner at the top of the st. Louis arch
Really is that possible and do other people do that? Yes. They do. There's a restaurant there
Yes, there's a restaurant there. I want to do with the person afraid of heights
Okay, I want to go out in the middle of nowhere like maybe the ocean
Guys guys can I stay with all of the I need to stay with people I can't afford a hotel
I got you
You got me? Okay. I got you. Okay
If you're gonna come out with this
Really
That's what he just said he can't afford to stay at a hotel
You'll pay for it. Oh, okay
Take the hotel man if it's paid for
go for the hotel Jesus goes don't don't get me I don't know psyche sometimes because you know I drink
uh I do a lot of cocaine I drink a lot if we did if your hand with me we're gonna do it
if he stays with you you're gonna do it is that what you get you know I'm just
psyche if you ever wanted to come over I would pay for it obviously yeah obviously stay with me
But don't use cocaine off my tool, I'll never degrade you like that.
You could do coke off my hand, brother, I'll do it off my own hand too.
You're gonna do coke off your butt.
Yeah
We can ask us if we want
I'll make an offer right now
Both know I'm good for it. I'll pay for
That's why you're a mob. That's why you're the best thing that is wants to come I'll pay for him too if you
Sure man to stay at a hotel
You're paying. We're gonna have to get some content in though. I see. I'm in a relationship. Okay, but you guys
You never download anything you never upload anything
You don't run
Fucking at the same time man. I don't know what the hell's going on
Uh, it's okay.
Jirai, now Jirai is fine.
See, every, see, Crystal Marie,
I happen to have a good mods right now,
especially if I'm a piece of shit.
Jirai, if they're not, like, doing anything wrong,
like, I really don't, you're not banned.
It was just timed down for 10 seconds.
Yeah, if they're actually banned,
like, I'll figure it out,
and I'll unban them by the next day,
or they can email me.
It's, it's, uh, Psyche at cultofpsyche.com,
and I'll unban you, and let me know.
But,
I have to trust my mods right now because I'm gonna do an all mod channel
I want to just be able to trust everyone so much, but they're my mods right at this point, right?
It was 30 seconds, so that's good. Yeah, I want to be you can always trust a Canadian
As far as far as you can go. I trust Canadians. Sure, man. Like anyone else. I trust a Canadian
I even trust racoon. I mean the only thing worse than a Canadian is nothing, but the second worst is Australia
3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3rd word 3
You're the reason why people sit out. Oh, it's all fit goes. It's not a real train station goes
And by the way, y'all your gate or your gate goes you you like there was
Because you had to admit you show me a picture of your penis and your toes
Now you've got to admit that you need to admit that that never happened
You know people are gonna clip this
You know that never happened people
You've never seen you never see much toes either
I have it here Mason. Can you get it? Yeah, I should that's a yo come again what?
Coming at my toes my penis. Oh my god
Hey, go get a go get a toes penis. How about that a toast penis a toast penis. What is that?
I don't know what that means. I don't know either. Why are you saying it? I think we keep TOS
Oh, peen toes misery knows I'm gonna I'm gonna mod misery peen toes
Toes peen toe
Have a toast those beans. Oh, I love that. It's a bean
Hey, I said my mind my mind about to explode
You know, it's things as you know, Christine quit ever to quit YouTube. What?
Christine
Yeah, I heard she deleted her channel or he did it anyways. He's still around
I don't know. I haven't seen her or heard anything. Okay. Yeah, toasted penis dry or penis toes
Yeah, I'm not sure. Have you heard of a Ted talk?
Pet talk Ted talk. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Ted talk a Ted talk Ted talk. Yes. I have
Confusing me. Are you talking about podiatry? You're not a foot. I said Pat Pat Pat like
Okay, now I understand now. I got it. Oh, you're talking in code of the language. I get it
Okay, what about Ted talk a pet doc?
We're putting them all away in a concentration camp. Okay. It's gonna be in Canada
Well, it's a lot to land up north go ahead. I said pet
Yeah, yeah, three minutes. Have you ever seen?
No country for old men. Yes. You like that movie?
It was yeah, it was different. Yeah. Yeah, okay. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I don't embarrass anybody, but I
Have a girlfriend. Okay
Why would that be?
Because you will think you will say I'm gay and then I say I'm straight. I don't know what I am. I'll say is I have
the fucking
Who is girlfriend in the world? Okay? Do you want to tell us who it is? No
But why is he Canadian? I said a girlfriend
I'm dating Crystal Marie
Crystal Marie know this no
I haven't told her
Misery said hi, I know I told you right, but he just had him out. Crystal Marie gonna come up. I might be bad
I just might be by I might be by
You know what I'm really into you like a little you like the chunky girl. That's okay
You're not gonna say it's like no here's what I'm into
I'm into crop tops
yoga pants. I
Like big video like you know blindfolds rope and
Submission
No, Crystal Marie's is funny right now. I'm so sorry crystal. Okay. Okay. It's a different crystal Marie. What is she finding?
Oh about the dating it's a different crystal Marie
That's Crystal Marie is my nickname for her. I'm not your man anymore. It's like you know Mason. I'm sorry. I
Have to break up with you. Why does she keep teasing like this Mason either get up here or shut the fuck up
Mason we're waiting for you
Mason why aren't you in backstage? I've got to post the link again. I'm in community is already posted it
Crystal Marie Crystal Marie is a bad. It's a different Crystal Marie. It's not Crystal Land
Of course, you know Crystal Anne said to me on her show
She said
Oh, thank you, you know, in real life, I wouldn't even associate with you.
I'm a higher class than you.
It looks like a literal blowfish.
I mean, I would eat your, I would literally cut this blowfish.
Organs out and eat them before I would lick chrysaline or sorry chrysaline
Aren't those fish poisonous? Are those the poisonous ones?
Yes, just like chrysaline, chrysaline has fucking poisonous. Oh ghost left, ghost has jelly
I always does that he just drops and then that's it. We're not gonna hear from him again for another day
Chrysaline, can you come up here at chrysaline?
Not my not my girlfriend chrysaline
the actual
Um, for some reason, I don't know where you're from.
I don't know. I don't want to talk.
I silly bastard. What did I do?
What did I do?
Sly bastard.
Yeah, I did rope over my level. I did.
Guys, I'm not as dumb as I look.
I know I look, I know I look really dumb.
I mean, really.
But there's a message in my madness.
Is there now?
How long does it take for it to become evident?
Okay, Chris and Marie is coming up. It'll take a few minutes. It's like Chris and Marie. Hey, what we're waiting for Chris and Marie?
I have a Chris and Marie song. Have you heard my Chris and Marie song?
Uh, I don't remember. Okay, I'm gonna find my Chris and Marie song. Hold on a second.
Hold on. I'm Chris and Marie. I'm gonna have a song about you. I think it's in here somewhere. I have to check my archive.
This is an introduction for a while. I'm gonna read it up.
M-A-R-A-M-A-R-R-P
Okay
okay I can't find it but I can play Christine versus Crystal and this I think
is Crystal are you losing your mind
Even my chickens live in a five star resort, right? Yeah, only your chickens, but not
Ozzy
I think that dog is the half you thought he was, he was supposed to be the cat
I didn't came up for a scene
So what's your cost, our resort?
The full perm.
What about this?
You're a dumb bitch for the last 10 months of fucking weeks.
You can't even fucking hurt yourself for the last 10 weeks.
Are you okay?
What's wrong with me?
I didn't run from jail.
I couldn't stop at 5 p.m.
She's never moving herself.
You talk a lot about yourself too.
I don't know, myself.
Well, she was trying to make everybody else be at me and ask them how come she can prove herself?
Well, she is like my best friend in her life, so I kind of know who she is
He said I'll never have your love I'm thinking why
Pretty cool in there
a lot of people are, but see these other people, I cannot do it because they're so fucking retarded.
They, they're not themselves. They fake themselves. Okay. Okay. They fake.
Okay, this bitch
I guess you know her like you know Marcy, right?
Well, these bitches do weird shit on the internet.
It's fucking weird, dude.
I don't know what the fuck is going on.
I can tell you, I don't know everything.
But she was made on the internet in the last 40 years,
everything.
You know her 12 accounts that she is acting as?
Oh, no. Oh, she has to have a cat. Well, you need to put me on game.
This is my friend.
Oh, my shit.
We're gonna do a whole lot of blast accounts.
Oh, you want to, you want to, hey, hey, bitch.
You want, you want a blast account right now?
She's got all my shit.
I want to know my shit.
That's what makes my fancy words.
I need some excitement today.
I've had a long week.
Oh, God.
Nah, that Christine shake,
I don't like that fucking backhanded compliment shit.
I don't like people that do that stuff,
that backhanded fucking compliment bullshit.
You know what?
I say exactly how I feel
and I don't wanna talk you again.
What it means, what it means that you suck.
I
You're being a bad friend to be that you're being a bad friend to our girl
Wait, Chris. I heard you say horrible horrible horrible. I love you
But I've heard you say a really bad thing.
I've never even said it.
You guys, Vita likes to go behind the scenes.
I don't like people that goes behind the scenes.
Crystal, Crystal, I've heard you say horrible things to Vita.
I've never said anything.
I might have said the B word like one time.
And then, oh, and then I never said it.
And then, I was, it's fine, it's fine.
I don't care what I was saying.
I heard you went crazy on Mother's Day
when you left them on panels.
be there somebody else thank you is i don't like these people i don't like the people that go out
for people to her people and like are like dirty disgusting humans like this guy he gives me bad
the birds
You really don't watch out look at his fucking face dude. He looks like he's gotta take a big huge shit
You have to take a shit everybody knows that we see it on your face. I just did like we see that shit on your face
Why are you trying to hurt my friend?
Just to piss you off
You just talked to God I got off the phone with him
Oh my god, I had standard okay, I mean I just wanted to show she was laughing and it was like you know
What was that big deal?
Articlown is here.
Hold on a second.
We have a guess.
I don't think the sound of the impression wasn't good.
Yes.
I think it's a sexy clown.
That's a good clip, though.
Articlown, are you here?
This is Articlown.
Hold on a second.
I hear the train coming.
Who's that?
Yo.
I saw you.
You're sexy.
Hey, what's going on, man?
Are you guys doing a wood up chat?
All right.
Oh, we have another guest. Oh shit our crystal Marie. Oh my goodness. Hello
Hi, you're sexy today. Good morning. Oh
I just woke up. I'm like I still don't have a way, so
What a smoke show my goodness
Whoa, all right. Don't don't ruin it
I'm sorry. Wow. No, I'm jealous cuz she has some pretty nice kids. I have to say
No, you kidding me. You're sexy hair. You look good Chris. So you're looking good as fuck. What'd you do?
Maybe say
Crystal turned psyche back to his normal setting
Oh my gosh, you're making me listen to drunk me
and
It was cheap, but have you seen this picture of salmon and and and an elbow?
What the salmon and I'll go kissing
When I first came around
Saman was mean to me. I
Hate Saman. Samans. He used to harass me for controller. Oh my god. He hated me for controller by the way
unbelievable
I called Ron, Barry, and fucking, what's his name?
The poor chop boys.
They used to be, they hated me, dude.
They wanted to kill me.
Ron, Barry, and fucking Eldo.
What is the poor chop place?
Is that what's happening?
They literally were threatening to kill me and shit.
It was insane.
They wanted $8,000 for them to stop using photos of me
or like, like,
I I a what is it AI photos of the fucking I don't even know it was it was like a
picture of Sigg and I mixed together and then they used it but then they say
it's me but it's definitely Sigg and I mixed together because NorCal made the
picture I know who did it I know what the fucking timeline I was there I fucking
know the fucking history okay these motherfuckers want to make shit up
Anyway, it's very frustrating. I know they do. I know they're so sick
What do you think about beta lately? Is she the new low cow?
She is yeah
This woman at a.m. I'm not gonna say her name. She said she said
Beta's then you give me the new big troll up the big new low cow. What do you think? Oh, I couldn't hear you
Do you think betas and little cow? I don't think so. No, no, I don't think so either
What guys I have to show you guys. I want I want to hear your opinion about about this because like
Controller
Vita doesn't do
She doesn't ask
She just like
Inserts retards in her life, and then they do the dirty shit
She doesn't do it purposely. I don't know if she does it purposely. I feel like it could be purposely. She's a psychologist
I'm not
Reading and serving guests
Good evening. Fight enough to eat today?
Boy, I'll say.
Well, that's great. Would you care for a time, repeat?
A little both, I think.
I don't wash my hands after using the bathroom.
Making friendly conversations like this is a big part of greeting and serving guests.
Our guests are usually dumb enough that you can distract their attention from our disgusting food with some meaningless banter.
Let's face it, working the carving station sucks.
You'll need to find ways to keep yourself interested.
This is the AI has been redone
You had the chance to spend lots of time with our customers
Remember, it's your job to distract them so that they think they are eating edible food
My dream the guest warmly and holding brief conversations as you serve them you say to our guests
Why don't you eat somewhere else and leave me alone?
Okay, I'll pause. I'll take it off.
You want?
Crystal Marie is not going to end up leaving.
She's going to end up...
Okay, I want Crystal Marie to leave.
I'll leave. You guys...
What?
Well, so Crystal Marie, obviously, you know,
Bita has been crushing out.
She's been flip-flopping on friends,
like it's fucking...
She's making pancakes.
You haven't called in like you used to into places...
Well, do you know...
Do you know...
Arthur that Sam man has been trying since he's been five or friends with Kate
He's been trying to fight with me every single day
Don't he's giving you a shout out?
Yeah, what's that all about if he's never mind trying to use her for content
He's like I had such a good time on a different panel and he got really pissed off of me
There's no arguing nothing
He found out that I was hanging out somewhere else and he fucking snapped at me. It was fucking bizarre as fuck
He's like that with the females here in the community. He gets very possessive
But yeah
So if he keeps making jabs, you know he jabs. I'm Molly walk. Okay. I'm Molly fucking walk
Well, I mean you took the vaccine all you want what?
Molly Wop all bow faces
Elbow to faces a thing that is elbow to
Face a Molly motherfucker Wop
Okay, yes, she's very
Cultured think that is thanks for dumbing it down for me Arthur. I got you brother. Look crystal Marie is a fine
Sorry woman. She is the ninth wonder of the world
Oh my gosh. Stop it, Arthur. You're making me feel uncomfortable.
I had the biggest crush on this woman here.
So, Crystal Marie, what are your thoughts on this season's Chiefs?
Are you betting this season? What are you doing?
Well, the season hasn't started.
It's about to start. It's about to start.
Well, they are in St. Joe. They're practicing.
killed his mother in minecraft yes oh in minecraft oh whoops
They're going through that I don't really know they're from Virginia um the assistant coaches
That's quite a quicky event fucking love the person
And that happened that guy's in training right now training his like players. He's the assistant coach
So his wife and his son which was in his 20s in college and they say he was a good kid
I don't know what happened
Off himself
No, he just he just shot
How can I say thank you? I love you. He tried to do something to his mother and he
That she's in now in critical condition and she got shot twice Wow
Our Kansas City
Assistant the second coach. Oh my god. He's uh his son
He's done shot
Prez Hills you hear about Prez Hills? Yeah, that's a spiritual war warfare. It's good your warfare. Okay. Yeah, that is definitely mason's
100%
Oh my god, did you guys hear that right before Christine left? She was saying that she was a Freemason
No, she's a star. Yeah, I I confirmed her about that. She admitted it. Yeah
Eastern star. She's an Eastern star and you know that women can't be free mason's. Yeah, they can't be Eastern stars
I should say there's Helen Bobosky was a
She was trans transgender
Hey
By man, yes, Chris summary I have one word for you women can be a part
Know but they're they give me eastern stars, but they're not yet or Dars of Job or but they cannot ever be a Mason
Yeah, but hell it's more like a witch Helena Blavatsky was a pre-mason, but she might have been
That's a witch. Yeah
Is that McDonald's cup purple or is it brown just looks purple and
Gold
Wow, those in the world. This is a magical brew right here. Hey, how about freemason right here 33?
There's a three right there
Let's play a couple cups
Hey
Hey, hey, you know what? I am not affiliated
But I am I am that shit that happened with press and that was um freemasonary bullshit
I know yes, but that is that is like
When you watch that, you're getting, you are getting.
Indomination, right?
Indomination.
Exactly.
Yep.
Thank you.
I know.
I don't know the exact termination, but I know exactly what I mean.
Here's what I am.
I am not affiliated with any organization, but I am above a 33rd degree Freemason.
I promise you.
Listen.
Even look at my all you do is look at my astrological chart. I'm above. I'm above
99% of all they claim most people are just porch mason's. Yeah, these big aprons with me with like the fucking compass in the square on it
This isn't I'm the real deal
Speaking of me. What the hell did he go?
Who Mason?
Mason, where are you?
Mason and drummer, of course the whole time
I need a blowjob
I found this image today, and I'm really disturbed. What is going on here? What are salmon and elbow doing in that picture?
And they scanned me out of a donation, by the way,
on a cash app and then laughed about it.
But you know what, who's gonna have the last revenge?
Right, right.
Oh my God, I saw you, Arthur.
I saw you.
You're hot.
Right, right.
I saw Arthur.
He's cute.
You see him?
He just came on the thing.
I don't remember making my penis.
I just bit a little lip together of my tape.
What that's crazy
You're gonna freak out like Crystal Marie. Come on. We don't want to
So crystal, um, do you know you don't call in as much as you used to all around
Like what's up with that? You've been you've been working a lot. You've been busy. You've been dating out in the real world
Yeah, I I really don't want to be I don't like being around because like it's just I'm just over round by it like
overran by haters there's too many haters I don't I don't feel like going on
people's panel to just fucking fight I don't have fun anymore what's the point
of going on if you don't have fun anymore I go to Sam in his chat animal
abuser pedophile I mean crystal
We knew from the get-go that this community was always gonna be a toxic
You know, we always knew that
Well, I know but it's a
Different situation
I got you you've got real things going on. I get it
Yeah, you gotta really watch out especially when you're female when there's real predators out there
There is trust me that Jane course black RG guy
I'm telling you right now, there's
BlackRG, this is my specialty, so BlackRG
He's a real predator
He is, go to Kennel Kickers on Kiwi Farms
BlackRG, he harasses a guy named Bill Chapin
He's a genius, he's an idiot, Savon
He plays the keyboard beautifully
Ivana is a real predator as well
Yeah, she sent me the pizza
What?
She's a sick bitch
You're lying.
I
No, no, all I said is that you're going too far. Crystal Murray is one of the
Originals here the OG's in this community. Come on down there
Come on now, brother
What do you say about black really care? Honestly, it's fine. Hey, but like our G our art the clown
He said something about black RG. What was that?
What black RG or somebody else about a punch. I said there's real predators out there
Yeah, I want to be I don't want to be involved black RG kind of guy named Bill Chapin Bill Chapin
Never didn't anything he got in domestic dispute. He's an Indian savant
He plays a really good keyboard. So black RG like had him play the song about the n-word and then he had him
Eagle matter into a store in his face. He had a go to Groovy Jimmy's house
and said Gary Coleman was there.
This is how sick that fucking N-I-G-G-E-R is.
Black R-G.
Oh my goodness.
Minecraft.
Well, do you think AI does not know
how to spell out the letters you're saying?
Yeah, I guess it's just saying the word that's the problem right I know
You know, Crystal, mind if I call you C.M., is that good with you?
Sure.
Hey, what's up, C.M.?
I miss you calling into panels.
Aw, thank you.
I miss hearing your voice.
You always enlighten my day.
And you've definitely made my Sunday surprisingly better.
So, thank you.
I'm sorry, not as nice as I used to be.
I used to be, like, more cheery, but it's, like, really hard.
It's all good. Your presence makes up for it. Oh
Bristol
Your bookie do you still have the same bookie? What are you doing? Well, my bookie's okay. I mean
the
You know there's a bunch of concerts going on out there in the real life
You got the you got the Chris Browns of the world the ushers of the world
The Shakira's of the world, I mean are you gonna go see somebody?
What about as far as beers are you still drinking any what was it that you used to drink or corona?
No, that's I mean I drink I'm really you know, I really haven't drank beer
No, you did you put the alcohol? I take shots. I
Don't really drink white claws or I drink tequila
Nice
Can you please get this out of my head are you Hispanic or no? I'm Spanish. Oh, you're Spanish. You're so you're like Christine
Portuguese and Spanish and
German oh your poor wow this woman has the best of all world to my goodness and
the food are you kidding me thing that is she has one of the best foods she's one
of the best foods which which the Portuguese the German the Spanish my mom's
first language is actually Portuguese hey are your mom's in X
Well, oh my goodness, no
Spanish woman
I'm exes Bolivian dude. Come on. It looks exactly like me actually my mom looks exactly like me
She had long hair. She had the same birthmark. We had the same arctic birthmark
We have the same
Everywhere
It's not you and that's her on Pamela. Well, my mom has been hurt
older she's an older woman okay well I'd love to meet miss Mrs. Crystal Marie
senior I'd love to introduce myself to her I'd love to show her that I can
provide for her daughter and I'll bring oh my god I'll bring a cow I'll bring two
chickens with me a goat you're gonna tell her about your wife too and a bag of
That's personal dude. That's minecraft
Sorry, sorry, it's okay. You hear about that Chris. It's okay. No my mom would shit on your cow
My mom would take a fucking gun out and start shooting at
Minecraft
Thank you
He destroyed your Minecraft house now you have to move into his basement
Now crystal, I know you used to dance back then on stream. Is that something you don't do anymore? Like
Stay away from that now
That's Chris the land Chris the land. Sorry. I know you you crystal Marie
You used to enjoy showing us your decorations for the holidays
Are you one of those people that believe in me? I'm gonna. I mean, I could do this a lot
I think me and blogger did the seawalk one time
I did like
I've tried to teach Jim Nick a line dance once.
What happened to Jim Nick?
Is she still around?
What's up with that?
Well, she was doing better than us because she's as far away the fuck away from Samman
as she could possibly be.
Hey, yo.
And he's not using her pictures anymore.
We're asking her and making her life worse.
You really don't like Samman, huh?
Well, not recently not for a long time not really for a long time. I don't like users
He doesn't have to use his friends for five dollars
Well, he uses me for 15
We use fucking elbow for five
To be fair, I don't even think he considers me a friend
Oh, we have it. Oh, I was in my queen's backstage. I mean, let me just, no, no, no, no, no, no. No, please, no
Thank you
No, he decided to pour him on me earlier. Now he wants to join in the fun
This is exactly how he's gonna sound watch. Hold on. Let me do his voice
He does not sound like that you guys
He does. He doesn't have money for 20 and he doesn't want to use it.
What's the matter with you? I've seen your sexy body. You want to go fucking lucky tonight. What's up?
He doesn't have money for 20 and he doesn't want to use it.
He's actually really nice to me
Let me just say Alexander early tonight. I let him up and he put a picture of a woman with a big black cock in her mouth
I'm like, what? Yes. That doesn't sound like a nice person. You want me to have him up now? He won tonight
He has to fucking
Kiss my toes before he gets back. We're just getting the balls from
It was a gift from an anonymous donator.
Oh, okay.
Here we go. I look at Tyler in the chat.
This is what he's gonna sound like.
Hey, hey, guys. Hey, Chris. Hey.
No, no, no. Yeah, you got it.
You got it almost right, Arthur,
but this is sounding in the background.
Hold on. This is sounding in the background.
Yeah.
Yeah. Now you got it perfect.
Okay. Yeah. Yeah.
It's like a year.
Oh, I'm ghost. Oh, I wanna, that's like a dick, oh.
I'm trying to be the cat.
Here we go, here's Ghost.
Hey! Hey, hey, hey!
Hang on, hang on, hang on, hang on, Ghost.
Hang on.
See, there you go, fucking dork.
Oh, wait a minute.
You dried up my pussy.
What?
You realize you're actually a fucking dork?
So it's like gonna be like $5 to kick in name one person I can fuck with me name one person I lost to debate you
Why don't you go for half an hour where'd you go for half an hour?
Well, why are you worried about it? I don't know where the fuck I want my grown-ass me because when you're not around I
Worry that's why
Yeah, well what I'm not around to get your ass. What bite, you know like it seems like I don't care about
You don't care about Maynay's? What?
You know what, fuck it. I will snitch him out of you.
Why do you think it clips in me? Alright, if you want to put it clips in me, I'm gonna go.
I'm talking to him.
Why do you want to put it clips in me?
Oh, come on, psyche.
No, oh, what the fuck? Oh, she don't like you. Damn, Lord.
Crystal, come back.
Well, that voice.
But draw with her. She was uh, she was uh, she was crying and talking shit about beat us the other day
Why is that bitch leave that bitch was talking shit about beat us the other day and now she's over here being civil that drunk bitch
Whoa, sorry crystals. I've been looking for the crystal Marie song. Can I run with the art to clown and can I run with like
non-american
Let me run more. I don't like Canadians matter like art to clown
You know thing that is the other day early to yeah, thank you early
And we already got to deal with the trains. I don't have to just extra but the other day and they're like
That was like four o'clock in the morning. I fell asleep. They're like, dude. You can't look at argue. Listen, I
Wake up looking for a law, you know, I'll wake not drama, but I wake up looking for it
that's not the way to say what you want to leave you gotta do
wait a minute, you made fun of Chris and Marie leave idiot, fuck you
well I tried to feed her, I tried to feed her some food, that's why
you tried to feed her some food? yeah, I've been starting to try to fuck
why do you wake up looking for a fight?
no, I don't wake up looking for a fight, I wake up looking for a debate
nah, yeah you say debate but you mean fight
Listen pussy you don't ever talk to me like that like you're talking down to me
I know what panel you've been on I can't I've been on second panel
So I'm a little slow, but you're gonna be this don't play with me. I've been watching you. Don't play with me
Am I not though by the way, you're talking which that's fine. You can talk shit
But am I not the only one that always tells you to come up always begs you to come up and my not the only one
Oh, please bring up the Canadian. Oh, please
You do it often yes, but you're not the only one
the debate with you but also I also tell you I'm probably the only one well
maybe not the only one but I'm one of the few always like oh start your own
panel oh we don't have to debate oh start your own panel you play whatever you
want to do like I'm just here to hang out did I not hang out with you on your last
panel yeah but again you're not the only one to tell me to do my own panel okay
that's true let me give you that I'll concede that but am I not the only one
Well
That one. Yeah, but got you there. Hey, that's where you've got your moment and got you
Is male join
Jay join the next one beta join the next one
So
You're not the only one to join the panel. Hello
You know what? It's been a long time
Talking to you and I'm talking to psych. It's been a long time. I think I'm not even at a permission
I think I'm gonna crash up
and you know who's getting it?
John Chugable, thanks for being here.
You, Ishmael.
I never saw such a good beard in my life.
My little dumb-dumb up here.
Look at that beard.
It's the best beard I ever saw.
Like Santa Claus, a young Santa Claus.
I love it.
I ain't asking permission no more.
I'm getting tired of it.
By the way, you asked me a good question like where were you the past three minutes? I went on to a
actual like
You know
Debate panel, and then I actually gave psyches
Thing I was like you come over here next to do it where they can't meet me
Where did you go with panel? I was starting to exiled
you. Oh, I was okay. Yeah, I'm
I'm not told to come over here.
Guess what? They're not coming
over here. Are you a bat?
He's not back but he's letting
us on though. He's letting us
on. They don't want to come
over and fuck with me. They
know better. You're not a
good guy. I fucked up. They're
ducking you, bro. They're
ducking you, bro. You put your
head on my show. Why would
I want more people. I like you a lot. I love you. And why'd you put a gun to your head on my show? I don't understand yet
Everybody do yesterday. How is everybody Saturday night? How was your Saturday night? It's all we use
It's all right, you know
Oh, great. Oh, so what's the matter? Why'd you shut up now?
Oh my bad. What's up? Did you ask me a question?
I said how was your Saturday, bro?
Pretty good pretty good. That's good, but I'm glad to hear that
It's good. It's good. You guys, you know, you're alive and well
You're alive and well
All you what happened? Did we scare go? No goes come back. I didn't mean to scare you bruh
Come on goes
So what people got going on?
What's this?
What is this?
Crystal Marie on a midnight stream.
Knee on eyes.
I'm going to go for a small one.
Talking coats in the desert saints.
Tattooed in maps and shaken hands.
She's got screenshots, names, and dates.
A tin foil halo.
Sealing fades in her chatroom, chapel, Saints confess
Every broadcast feels like a holy mass
She's cookie, she's heart, she might be right
Dropping bombs in the middle of those black pants
Symbol sex, oh lord, what will she say next?
Crazy Colts gang
and traffickers
Great music, I'm digging it. I'm digging it, you know everywhere as I go people want to know
psyche
Don't know what's going on with the panel channel today. It's everybody's got that low-tier energy
Everybody's got low-tier energy right now, bro
What's going on, bro?
It's all like you guys like what's going on you guys on nightclow
You guys need some caffeine. I'll get you some caffeine, bro
Come on boy. You're on the psychic panel channel. You got to get amped up
Yeah, you gotta do some salsa. You gotta get riled up. You got to cook somebody
Go out with this low-tier energy, bro
Sniff some more sabi
Look at that chick riding that rocket to the moon
Got it. That's how they ride my rocket. That's exactly how they ride my thing
You can tell I'm giddy up, giddy up on that thing.
Little rocket.
I don't think you understood what I meant, brah.
Definitely not what I meant.
That's not what I meant by it.
That's how she rides my rocket.
That's not what I meant, brah.
We're way over your head there, old timer.
Attractable, where's that energy at, brah?
Where's your energy at, attractable?
Are you doing guys?
Oh look it's Daryl!
Daryl's in the building!
Are you doing money or what?
Sound like you're scuba diving bro, I can't hear you.
I'm all snorkel though.
Still can't hear you bro, sounds like you're locked up in a secluded room bruh.
I'm locked up wherever I wanna be.
Daryl! Daryl!
Eat your bike Doug!
Came here to my show?
Is that Daryl?
No it's Daryl!
There's a gank that all might of me
No, I like to be a bike wiping your ass
But you say hey, yo
I'm finna crash out. Hey, yo
I like this guy Daryl. I like this guy Daryl right there. Hey, hey, how are you?
Can I call him in that word? No, you cannot because I told you you can't say that word.
This is my brother Daryl. This is my other brother Daryl. It's Bob Newhart.
That's just my baby doll. You want to say Bob Newhart?
That's just my baby doll. You said Bob Newhart, Daryl?
Can I call my maggot? Okay. It goes here. You're you're you're one step away. I
Said maggot. Hey, stop doing cocos. We're having a fun time
Hi, Darrell, I didn't think I'm right
Yeah, bless. I'm blessed. Nice
Unchalkable pace can somebody come over here to run one with me
Oh, my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my
Yeah, go on. Why not?
If you got one, don't be shy.
Who wants a line of Coke? I'll do Coke.
Why not?
Coke, I miss my 20s. I think I would do a wedding one.
And they actually had a coke dealer as one of the wedding guests.
You know their association except he had to just coke.
And that wasn't good.
By the way.
It wasn't you guys, it was probably your older brother or something like that.
It wasn't me. It wasn't me.
It wasn't me.
Like 20 lines of a toilet seat that night. It was the best night I've ever had.
I thought they were smoking Alicia Cousin.
Who's cousin?
Alicia. Alicia Teebum?
Let me see at least Alicia Elijah the Bible from the Bible or lead a different Alicia. Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, the guy from the Netherlands
So Darrell, where are you from? I thought you're Mexican, but we're England from England, mom
Hey, so I went to Manchester. I've been to London my mind. I went to Canal Street a man. Everybody can Alstreet
anymore
Canal Street in Manchester
Oh, well, well get go where the gays go. I've been the good with a gaze
I'm my brother-in-law
Street
So I
And I went and I went to canal Street and there was this big leather guy and he was like you're hot
You're so cute. I kind of got scared
And everyone was looking at my wiener in the bathroom.
It was great fun.
Okay, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry.
I know you're the one who's in the house.
It was great fun.
You've been a high moment in your life, Tyche.
I've been a high moment in my life.
It was great fun.
I mean, I get to train from London to Manchester.
I get to the ferry to Belgium to Bruges.
It was great fun.
And then I went to Amsterdam and I got lost there for about a couple of months.
And then I went to the Czech Republic.
and also the love parade in Germany that was the red light district bungee
being a program no they didn't ban me but i did go there one time and it's like i was just a
couple other guys i had to go with the prostitute so i was in the door i was completely limped
i like i like i was like let me give you an ecstasy and coke and then i was like here's
I mean, it was a bad bit.
They went to tie chicks, and they didn't want you,
because you had a small dick.
Yeah.
Well, it was a little jazz.
You're a gloat.
Yeah, you're a gloat.
You're a troll, man.
Do you have a wife?
No song?
Look.
Oh, we're child, we're child.
Be careful.
Oh, we're here to go on.
Bata school.
Oh, what's up, psych?
Yeah, we're here to go on Bata school.
Wife's butt.
Hey baby, how are you doing today?
His wife is here, so he's just supervising again. It's like an adult supervision
Somebody talk to my bitch
She's nice
Who you gonna fuck
I'm happy to be back in a minute.
Anyways, like I was saying,
the thing that is, that background
is very surprising.
What a crowd.
Yeah, I like it.
You're supervised on the show from now on.
You need your wife's supervision,
and you can't be on the show otherwise.
Good morning, reality Nancy.
We're having a good day.
Hey, it's a good day,
because we banned Alex McQueen finally.
I'll let you back on.
You say it again.
Your ass is off here.
Everybody relax.
Everybody gets excited when they see something.
No, it's coming out.
It's coming out.
Don't get excited, because you've got a woman moderator.
Why didn't you tell you?
Why didn't you tell me?
Thank you.
You're the one
No pussy though. We'll start back when I'm over the wrong pussy. You're the one flashing it
You're you're flashing pussy
You look on my TV, I ain't got no teeth
My girls push you right now
I mean, it's shocking
Why do I keep getting kicked out for being too real?
You get no big
Are you right next to you? Yeah, you guys got no bitches. That's what it is. You got no bitches
My bitch
That's your bitch or Smurdoff. That's nothing, bro. I would drink that shit like nothing. That's my bitch
That's your bitch
I got a real vagina next to me
Wow, wow
But China next
enjoy it bro
you see what Saki is doing
if you got that grash enjoy it man
but not that impressive
enjoy it
enjoy your pepper on the pizza together
hey untrackable you get it don't you
I can see by your snigger on me
you get it
hey Saki I can't wait
untrackable gets it man
I'mma bring you over here
bug saying bro
look like you got lipstick on
I'm sorry. You look like you don't
know. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
How are you doing tonight?
Hey sweetie, can you tell your man a little bit?
I know he gets too, too crazy.
Yo, stay on camera.
Everybody's been on camera tonight.
You want me to show it?
You want me to show you his titties?
Yeah, I see them.
Oh, damn.
Oh, fuck.
This is a camera-only panel, guys.
Guys, this is the most rare thing in the panel.
Yeah, I love your handsome man.
You know?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Fuckin drinking Clorox
Fuckin about sexy ladies
Your woman look like a plank
Fuckin drinking Clorox
Nigga, what's up?
Fuckin about sexy ladies
Such a dirty ass sub nigga, what's up?
Nigga we have no pussy than the pussy you've got bro
What's up?
You flexing pussy like you got pussy
Nigga we have no pussy than that
So hot
Nigga we have no belly than that
Oh baby, oh fuck
Oh baby
Whoa, he's so hot. She's finna jack me up. It's a hot tamale right there Mrs. Glow.
That's why I told you I told you psyche I can't busy you.
I know if you visit me I'm gonna have to lick your butthole.
Are you gonna help are you gonna help Dina? I'll help her whatever she wants me to I'll be the I'll be the landscaper for
She'll be the head
Give me the contractor. I'll be the judge. Let me just let me use a leaf blower. Look at Dina. Look at Dina
Wow, oh my god
I got to get open it's gonna blow
you're making me more and more weeds
what are you talking about
I didn't see
hey hey I have psychies real address
we live next to each other
don't tell them
we don't need to know
we're without the gun though
I'm never gonna
expose my boy
I love my boy
my psychies my boy
I'll only expose myself to you in private with your wife.
I love you, dawg. I love you for being real, my boy.
Listen, even if it's all jokes. I have a good sense of humor. I have a fucking good sense of humor. I promise
I love you for being real, bro
Hey, hey, you know what? It's like I'm at it sick, but you know, even if whatever you did
I forgive you because you're really cute. I forgive you for being white
Okay, you can have your French kiss
I forgive you for being gay, boy
You gotta double kiss me with my girl
Go on, you've got a girl there, yeah, but you still come across gay.
We have to have a three-way kiss.
You've got a girl there, but you come across gay.
Okay, it's okay. Can you pull up your shirt again? I want to see your nipples.
Oh, baby.
Oh
I think it is. I think it is. I feel violated right now. Oh my god.
I feel exhausted.
Daryl, have you ever had a bike experience?
You feel like you're missing teeth?
Well, I'm missing more now.
But you're in glow. Have you ever seen a guy through in glow?
Shit. If only I had a sexy boomer with a smile.
You're missing teeth is crazy.
Go on, go on.
Who has a gay experience? I have.
He does it.
But he can't say it. Don't be me.
I have a picture of your tail
I'm not gonna attend to nothing
That's what we said, you look like your bestie
There, there
It was all good in bed
Okay
Who needs to take one of John?
This is the best time of my life
That's cool
I just need my best friend here
Avieta?
That means close the door?
Okay
All right, then, so Daryl, Daryl dropped off.
He finished, I think.
Okay.
Now let's go for three and a glove.
I don't know.
It's a joke, it's a joke.
Why are you the track boy? You look so stern and trackable. I want to hear what it was like starring in
Yo, it's like yeah, you doing today on a Sunday. It's happy Sunday. I feel like
It's like he can we hang out today? Yeah, it's Domingo. You know something go. Can I buy a pizza for us?
And we're getting out only back into your wife's fish taco and you know, I'm not I'm not gonna drink
Can we are you gonna hang out? Yeah, but I'm already drunk. Oh, but don't let me drink
I won't I won't but it's impossible
Like I could let you drink psyche and drink your if you want to suck me up fuck it
Better share you better share with
I got your address, you know that right
Hey, I gave it to you for a reason. Yeah, I'm ready for the tree. I'm not gonna be mean
I'm not gonna be just
Don't be rough, but just be gentle. Okay, I'm gonna bring pizza over and fucking
Okay, I want a pinga. I want to I want a
I know Spanish
Pinga Kulo and
You know how to suck it right?
I was born to suck.
Nah, I was born to suck.
You better know how to suck it right, alright?
Cause my girl's gonna get real mad if you don't know how to suck it.
Don't say you got it.
I'm going to shut up. I'm going to be a silencio. I'm going to be a silencio better, okay?
I don't know what you're saying. You don't know nothing.
I don't know. I need to learn from Spanish people. I want you to bring a leaf to it.
Hey, 300 globe. What the fuck are you talking about?
Hey
I don't have to put a leaf blower
Okay, yeah. Okay, Silencio you're not saying nothing. Say that
Oh, we have RG here
I'd be like, you're not stable
She's a bad olympic, it must RG
Baby, that's true
RG is cool
RG, yeah, RG, if you're not cool
and if you guys don't look at you on the desk remember
I'll let you back up
Come on, all of you up RG, get to be cool
Because I've added it's a new day.
RG, can you fuck up?
I'm gonna get you off.
I'm not going to point about it. I just want to say that NorCal never edited a pic of chrysalmory
That's just her without makeup without her teeth in and she can't handle that fact
That's what she looks like with no makeup
Really, I wouldn't be with you keep saying I look 60 years old and I suck at my shows over
That's I'm sorry
Oh, you should change your diet and maybe exercise a little bit
you you look when you're 60 okay you're out of the show yo psyche you on the
house there no you have a house here we have crystal back on the stage I mean
RG you missed out I mean I say oh what's up I don't hey I just want to say
that guy's a fucking liar dude I don't have to think any fucking thing I don't
have to look anyway I know exactly what they did in my picture and what they you
Hey
We want to see how big your tits are
You don't you just leave if you don't want to show you
What I'm saying is that guy is so but hurt because Ivana is having freak off
You guys know that black RG is dating Ivana
I want to see you. That's why
You're cute as well. This is very cute. I'm ready to come on you
Me and Dina are gonna double TV there psyche
You hear me okay, even though I 48 people
I don't want to get too crazy because I went through your glow to come here and put his lingua in my
Coolo
I'm gonna bring 7-eleven hot dogs over and you're gonna suck me up
You're gonna lick my ass because I'm not licking ass
Like you can we get him out of here. We're talking crystal. We kind of talk in this guy. What do you mean?
Get him out of here
If that bitch ain't showing Teddy's
What do you mean it's not porn bombing you I don't know why you have the blocker up we're where's crystal there she is
Take the makeup off and show people you really look like
Because we've seen it there is no
she does that make sense I'll give you that
she has boobs
she went to Tijuana, Mexico
to get her boobs done
that's all she's really good for to be honest
I wanna see the boobs
are they big? probably
probably are big
I wanna see the boobs
she wanna see one of the boobs done
fuck it
hey, hey Psyche
can we see her boobs?
sure, what the fuck
What are you doing psyche?
Get him out of here site
He just loves attention
No, it's like you're sake you can't do that when I visit you
I'm sorry. I was thinking about speaking my pen. You gotta stop bending over when I visit you today
I'm gonna bring over pizza and some drinks
What you know, I have psyches address. No, I have psyches address and I got the pizza spot
Okay
Yeah, you know sometimes I question myself. What am I doing in life?
You know what you're doing you're the best show on YouTube and don't forget it
Forget that fucking bitch beat in Sam and they're just a bunch of n-words. Okay. Oh my goodness Minecraft
No, no, no as an n-words
Minecraft yo, Brian Rizzo yo Brian Rizzo you're fucking lucky
Well, fuck you middle
If you get the rest of the show without putting a gun to your head or poor bombing
I'll fuck the shit on you Brian
Hey guys, don't you just question yourself around with a little we're awake. What's up?
Hey, it's 6 a.m. Over here. What time is it where you guys are at?
It's 6 30 over here. What time is it over there? Hello?
Hey, I'm track the ball. What time is it over there?
I'm on the East Coast, so what time is it over there?
But I'm on the East Coast. It's over here 6 35 a.m. Where were you at? What time is it?
You just said East Coast 935 idiot do the math. I don't know the East Coast. Fuck the East Coast.
Get the sake take it get him out of here. Fuck the East Coast nigga.
I'll give a shit dude, fuck you
Fuck the fuck you live
You're in the glove, you're in the glove
I'm literally working on a song right now
Don't porn bomb or do anything bad
And I'll have a song for you in your life
I'm not doing nothing bad bro
No, no, that's not me
What's wrong with you guys let my boy psyche on your fucking loser, dude
Fuck I'm here, but I'm ready a song about you back. I'm not a loser
Actually, I have a good job
Fucking Trump wants out of here. I actually get paid 75 dollars an hour. I actually have a good job
Bucket. Well, why are you guys so embarrassed about it?
Hey
If you want to wear lipstick that that's on you
Well, so what's up with your boy right here? You're just letting him talk shit to me
Well, you're a loser dude. Fuck you. I'm not bro. I actually have a good job
Why are you hating on me?
Gonna glow I'm making more money
Behave yourself for four more minutes. I have such a good song for you coming up. Just a way
Yeah, I should behave myself, huh
Suckie how much to get him out of here, dude. I'll give you five bucks
Then throw it throw the five bucks
Fucking niggers
I'm going to put the song about you anyway, but you and you're going to make a song.
I wrote it for the don't play it.
It's that easy.
Stop.
No, you're calling the cops. You're like the 9-1-1 nigger.
9-1-1. 9-1-1.
I ain't calling the cops. I'm about to call ICE on you, nigger.
Fuck you, nigger.
Whoa!
Dude, he keeps calling me...
Oh, my goodness.
Untrackable. What's up, brother? How you doing there?
I'm doing very well. I hope everybody's enjoying their day.
You know finding a way to put a smile on their face
Untrackable if I were to have seen you in the woods, bro, I would shit myself. I don't even know
And I'd probably help you clean it up and get you out of the woods dude, I'd be so terrified all my goodness
I don't know. I don't know.
How you doing arturo? Oh, I mean I'm banned over there at beaters as you may know
Yeah
Banned me be that's a recurring thing though, which is so stupid. You know why her her reasoning is because you keep looking
It's like I brought her up in a conversation she was in and she was present
And you're telling me I'm banned because of I'm bringing up your friend first of all I mentioned
Oh my god, yo this woman got a fat ass
She's like you brought up my friend, bro. You literally put up people on panel who have doxxed
Have doxxed you have doxxed people on panel have doxxed people in your chat have doxxed your mods
like what?
There's people there that threaten her
Meanwhile me I bring up her friend and I'm banned
there's people who have porn bomb her with their own bodies
there's people there who have said the n-word
there's people there who have wished harm on n-word
like what are we doing in our band?
does that not make any sense?
I don't know what to say Arthur
all you have to do is pull me up to 25 bucks, dude, in your own bed.
All you have to do is pull me up to 25 bucks.
No sense.
I'm this bad, big, evil girl.
All you have to do is pull me up to 25 bucks that you'll never do.
RG, you don't have to say about you.
Dude, what's the feedback?
RG real quick.
RG, shut up!
Okay, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG, RG
RG is a smart person, he has good points, and he's funny.
And it's like, and I like you.
You've been on, you've been on the show
since almost the beginning.
I don't know how you kind of turned on me.
I know when it was the Branding Cupid.
I hate that fucking M.F.R. now.
Everyone told you about Branding Cupid.
Yeah, I know, but don't say I told you,
so that's the most annoying thing.
I'm writing, I'll write a song about RG too.
if you wait around okay I'll write it I don't want a song at all okay get out of here get out of here
I have one about okay so I have an untrackable song I have and I have a
300 glow song RG you don't want it okay fine I'm not gonna fucking force you okay
but I have an untrackable song and I have uh I mean I just tried to compliment the guy and
like try to make peace but it's like you know what just like I did with Boston Bridget I was like
let's make peace no no no it's like no no no make peace I mean I try
I apologize, I say something nice, and it's still fucking fucking me over, okay?
So whatever, RG didn't just whatever.
You know, I tried to like, you know-
Oh, I know what it's talking about.
Hey, do you have the Christmas song still?
Or you stole Christmas?
Oh my god, you're sexy as fuck.
I was saying the thing, it makes no sense.
She bans me, but she licks all all of these people on panel.
It makes no sense, dude.
Like her standards are you brought up my friend and I told you to stop. That's the worst thing you could do like what?
The thing whenever I say man, I can't change your mind
And if I even fucking try and talk to her about it, she's just gonna get mad at me
So can we agree though that that makes no sense?
There are people that have done much much much. It might be a little harsh. Let me put it that way
it's a little hard
Yeah, I don't think he's actually like damaged. Let's say
Awkward just really awkward. No, there's no way dude. He's like a 30 40 year old who doesn't know what pussy is
Like come on dude. He's clearly mentally. He's not okay. And and it's like
Like, bang, like, look, I love the story of the pod, trust me, I love to talk a lot of
shit.
But where I cross the line is, one, people's helps, like, for example, what Christine was
saying, like, people make fun of her with, like, some chirping sound.
Knowing that, I'm not going to fuck around with that.
You know I love to mess around with Christine, but I won't.
I do not mess with people's health, people's health, or their obvious state of-
What's the chirping sound? What does that mean?
That was hilarious.
Okay, okay, I have Three in Glow's song is coming up.
Okay, are you ready for Three in Glow's song?
I think it's almost ready.
Okay, it's almost ready.
That subtitle's getting rendering it.
Okay, so it's almost there.
And Untrackable, you're next.
Untrackable, you're next.
Three in Glow, I want you to hear.
Three in Glow, wake up.
Where's your wife?
Where's Warkie?
Señorita Glow, señorita Glow,
¿Cómo estás?
Bien, gracias, aquí, aquí, aquí.
Por favor, caliente, arriba, arriba, arriba.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yep, for sure. Okay. It's ready. Okay guys. It's ready guys and everyone says I suck and I have no talent
Just take it just say clear oh hoes on this. Okay. Oh, it's on this. It means eyes in Mexican
Okay, ready here we go. It's ready
Okay, got it. Ready
Ready slow just sit there watch it. Okay, so yeah, show me psyche look
Who's that kid? Who said that to me?
Hello!
They got an A.I. fan made out of me.
300 gloves!
I'm here to have fun!
All the life fucking dies!
I'm here to have fun so I fucking die!
Fuck it!
Thank you, Max!
Here to shake ass!
Let me shake ass!
Show me four screens!
If you make me scream, I wanna shake ass.
Happy nigga, I'm down to die.
I'm not scared of death.
Shout out to my dad, shout out to my mom.
I love them.
I love my mom and my dad.
Oh well, nigga, it's time to go.
Y'all, put me up nigga.
I'm ready to shake ass.
What is this?
It's me, Roni. It's me, bro.
What? Why?
As you pour them on me, and then you...
So what, dick? So what?
I'll be...
Come back later. We're having a party here.
Okay? We're having a party.
Yeah, we're having a party.
That was untrackable's turn, okay?
Don't be interrupting my party.
You get it. You get it. You get it.
Hey, Saki. Hey, Saki.
When you die, I'mma be at your funeral.
I'mma be the main one.
Shaking that and I want you to be in a mariachi and play mariachi music. Yeah
Yeah, okay. No, I will I will do that now. Um, now I'm untrackable your song is
Hey, I spent my time in West Texas. So got a little bit. Yeah, when you die nigga
I'm gonna grab you by your beard and fucking just bury you. Thank you. Oh my god
Right
It's okay. It's okay guys
This is the last one and then I have to go because I'm gonna get a little too drunk and too crazy
And I need to like freshen my butthole for three and a little bit. Oh, yeah, let's do this
It's me. So this is this is gonna be a trackable song. Okay. You're ready for a trackable song. You're sure
Let's go
You like this is a glow. Did you like that? Did you like?
Green glow song. I'll play it again
It's the same one, right?
Same one.
I don't know.
I'll add it right.
I want to add that.
It's the same one.
They tried to find him in the woods one night
Speak beer gone
Trackable off every map big foot saw him and said who's that chap?
Footprints so large they block the trail his beard has its own zip code and mail
Build nest when he falls asleep park rangers whisper don't wake that beast a saddle beans then law the signal behind his beard on screen
What he put in the brew one taste of breakfast made the sergeant look is this an
odd pace he said that information is classified just taste his biscuits were
strong enough to stop a tan smoke and served it as child untrackable thousands
of days he said thermal cameras failed when he walked through the snow they
only caught a beard with two boots below last seen grilling somewhere off grid
Untrackable king of the bacon and cooking half grizzly bear untrackable legend of the get you
The beard just a polo a polo it's already warm. I do one more song for a polo
I think I can do one more for a polo. Okay. I did you when you like that untrackable though
Okay, you left. Okay. That wasn't up for him or no. He's still there. There he is. Do you like that untrackable?
Okay, I'm doing one more song for a polo
I just need to put some information, hold on a second.
Okay, I got all the info on Apollo.
I got all the intel on Apollo right here.
Okay, let me see.
Okay, one second.
I mean, it's a five step process,
but I'm very, very fast at it.
Okay.
And Dragon, would you like that?
Okay, I got it, I got it, I got it.
It's already done, it's already done.
Okay, I mean, it's not already done.
It's like I still have a little bit more to do.
Hey, are we good?
Oh, it's just you and me.
It's you and me.
know Alexander McQueen I'm gonna need an apology I'm gonna need a promise you
basically you know Alexander McQueen you did me wrong to that you poor mom me
that could take away my whole channel I mean if I wasn't smart enough but I am
take fortunately but I mean geez Alex I mean you had to poor mom me with a big
black dick in some woman's mouth okay Apollo your song is ready I'm gonna I'm
Make it real quick. Okay, and I'll teach you how to do this
But you guys if you will have to hire me. I'm like a few bucks now. Okay. Anyway, I will teach you how to do all this shit
I promise you
Really fast. Okay. Okay, so ready Apollo. Okay, so Apollo this was like about
Three minutes, okay, let's take that. Okay
guys, but I say I'm good. I don't exaggerate. I mean, I don't want to like, you know, give
myself away. But yeah, I'm pretty good. Okay. And so let me see. Okay. Hello. And I think
what style are you? Okay, I added your style.
Okay, so I
Drop I'll let you finish the song. I'm gonna draw a game. It is. You know, you're my you're my best friend
I love you. Okay a best friend. Wow. I said one of my best friends. Oh one up. Okay. I have a lot of them
Okay, but you're okay. That's good. Hey, I like you do. Okay. All right. I like to take care. I'll talk to you later
Bye kisses. What is it?
You're not gonna forgive me and so that's crazy. Oh
Now you're now you have regrets don't you I do yes
Okay, I want I want I want I want the most sincere apology and a promise never ever to do me wrong again
I mean, you're not gonna be a mod, but I need even to be allowed. Oh, no, no, no, that's what we go wrong
Okay, okay, get out of here. Get the fuck out of here, bitch
This is my show go go over to your your buddy money for 20 you betrayed me for a little you little
New York cop bitch. Oh
Fuck all in your cops of their bus
Okay, don't fuck with psyche. Listen. Listen. I'm a national treasure. I promise you this is my last song of the day Apollo
Here's your here's your link. Okay. I want to follow up here for a song. Okay. There you go. You got the other link, okay?
Okay, now I'm gonna make the song for Paul, okay.
Is it ready?
It's almost ready.
Paul will just take five more.
I said I wanna put a video to it.
Hey, get out of here, Alex.
You can come back later.
You have to apologize.
I know Alex sounds like he's in regret.
This is the last song of the evening,
even though there's four people in chat
and this is awesome.
And I love this, having four people.
I can't, I mean, I'm trying my best
to stay as long as I can.
Road Nomads here.
I might have to do a rogue nomad song, but only if he comes up and talks to me and
Apologizes for all this bad shit. He said about me on beat his panel over and over and over again
You can come up get to apologize to me though guys
Listen, I don't play I'll I'll make a good song for everybody for free and stuff. Yeah
I don't know. It didn't make Untrackable leave. I mean, Untrackable, I think, come and go find his wife to make another baby or something.
He loved that song. That was a Bigfoot, Untrackable's Bigfoot. Apollo, it's, listen, listen, Apollo's song is special.
Rogue Nomad, you want one too? Apollo!
Hey
I need to come up
Yeah, I made it. I made one for you and we'll take it maybe like maybe five more minutes
Trust me
Well, you know what?
I love it. I've been to Greece. I've been to Greece.
This is the world. This is the time. This is the place. This is the motion.
Okay, the year's only special. It took me a little longer than the usual days.
Okay, so Rogue Nomads, since you said no, you're being kicked out of the chat.
Sorry, you're being banned for the time being.
Maybe I'll ban you later, but yeah, just for being a dick.
Um, yeah, you're kicked out of the chat and you're not getting a song.
Okay, Apollo, your song's ready, okay?
Your song is ready, but I have to make the video for it.
So, I'm gonna make the video.
No, no, it's okay. I'm excited.
No, no, no, no, no.
No. Hey, Apollo, I already wrote this song.
I mean, as a man, I've got to make the video for it.
It'll take just a couple more minutes.
You're ready for this? Are you sure you're ready?
Okay, I'm gonna...
Okay, this is my last song, okay?
My son and my wife are listening too.
Okay, this is the last call.
I'm excited.
The last call, and then I'm going to leave.
I'm going to leave.
It's okay.
No, no, no.
Your song is almost done.
It's almost done.
I promise you.
It's okay out.
I know.
And Rogue No Man, you know, go, go, go, go, go.
Let's beat it for a song.
Yeah, yeah, go here. Here's your girlfriend. I'm trying you stupid MF for
Road Nomad. Here's your girlfriend right here. What do you see your girlfriend?
This is who you're choosing over me
Okay, it's mine. It's fine. Hey, hey, hey, your songs your songs just about ready Apollo and this will be my last
Okay, hey
I'm a I'm a big. Um, I'm a big, uh, Mari cone. No, no, that's not the right word. Hold on. Let's see
How do you say how do you say f a g and and what do you forgot how you say it? I forgot how you say it
Okay, wait call me. I know I see you Alex back state. I love you Alex. You love you
I still love you Alex, but you know, hey guys
Listen, everything was jokes. Everything is in good humor. I will forgive most people
I will need an apology from some people, and if they don't want to give it, it's fine.
Just don't come here anymore.
Okay.
Apollo, are you ready?
I'm excited.
You're excited?
Okay.
Good.
I would say about 20 more seconds, and we're going to be, okay, it's ready already.
You ready?
I don't believe it, in a few minutes.
I got you, no, no, I got you right now, it's ready.
Okay, here we go.
It was the last song of the evening that I'm gonna take off.
But I, um, hey, I love you guys.
Don't delete it.
If I like it, please don't delete it.
Please.
I won't.
From Mount Olympus to the YouTube screen.
That's what?
Maria, Maria.
Oh my God.
Spartan heart.
Walks in the room helmet shining confidence bright ask him who one he's always right
Summer sees him coming and rolls his eyes Christine says here come another ten replies. He lifts his shield
Oh jesus christ
Oh my
Comments keep track, keyboards glow, nobody remembers how the arguments start.
Oh god.
I hate you.
Oh
Man I would love I would like you to say
Understatement I would love it seriously gay give me a link please please. I beg you. I beg you
And in few minutes fuck you man fuck you
I mean, I'm not as dumb as I look. I know I look at a dumb, but I'm I'm actually
Unbelievable we love it over here. So please give me a link somehow
Just please, please, I'm begging you, please.
I gotta put it backstage for you, hold on a second.
Okay.
Oh my goodness.
Seriously, see?
That's what I mean.
All these hoes, you know, the shit thing they are waiting for drama,
at last you continue to do something by your own.
Create content.
They have some kind of continent. I think I mean I I like myself. I mean, I think I'm good
Okay, so I'm putting this thing think backstage for you and there you go
And thank you very much. I will repay you. I will trust me
It's okay. Okay. I love you. Wow
Everybody here, okay
Okay, it's okay. I don't know if you have to go up you have to go
Wait wait I didn't download it. Yeah, yeah, I got the link. I got the link. Thank you very much, man
So really appreciate it. Yeah, you got it. I gotta go but I'll be back and yeah, it's okay
Maybe I'll make a song for you for anything else. Thank you for being here guys. I love you. Oh my goodness
Have a good night guys. Ciao. Ciao. Have fun. Have fun. Have a nice day